A Guide to the John C. Watkins Papers 1979-1999
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series II-Office Files 1984-1997
  - ABC Revisions 1987 (Box 34)
  - ABC Stores 1983-1986 (Box 34)
  - ABC Wine 1983-1994 (Box 34)
  - Abortion 1993 (Box 34)
  - Access to Court Records 1997 (Box 34)
  - Acts of Assembly 1991 (Box 34)
  - Administrative Process Act (BH 1181) 1991 (Box 34)
  - Adoption-Foster Care 1994 (Box 34)
  - Agenda 1994 (Box 34)
  - Agriculture 1993-1997 (Box 35)
  - Agriculture Deduction (HB 1279) 1993 (Box 35)
  - Agricultural Research 1988-1992 (Box 35)
  - Agriculture Tax Deduction (HB 1382) 1989 (Box 35)
  - Airport Authorities (HB 631) 1990-1991 (Box 35)
  - ALEX 1997 (Box 35)
  - Alternative Medical Practice 1996 (Box 35)
  - Amber Lights (HB 415) 1986 (Box 35)
  - American Legion Baseball Team 1986, 1992 (Box 35)
  - Animal Health Lab 1995 (Box 35)
  - Answered Correspondence 1997 (Box 35)
  - Any Willing Provider (HJR 231) 1996 (Box 35)
  - Appointments-Governors 1997 (Box 35)
  - April-Correspondence 1987-1988, 1992-1996 (Box 35)
  - April-Correspondence 1996 (Box 36)
  - Arbitration (HB 960) 1984 (Box 36)
  - Arbor Day (HB 1587) 1993 (Box 36)
  - Assembly Press Clippings 1989 (Box 36)
  - Assembly NP 1995 (Box 36)
  - Assessments Districts (HB 1501) 1991 (Box 36)
  - Assessments for Local Improvements (HB 1409) 1989 (Box 36)
  - Attorney General 1992 (Box 36)
  - Audiologists (HB 379 and 272) 1992-1993 (Box 36)
  - August Correspondence 1987-1988, 1992-1995 (Box 36)
  - August-Correspondence 1996 (Box 37)
  - Automobile Dealers 1992 (Box 37)
  - Auto Rental Companies/Insurance 1996-1997 (Box 37)
  - Bay Act Criteria (HB 1663) 1991 (Box 37)
  - Bay Acts Grants 1991 (Box 37)
  - Bay Act Ordinance (HB 1945) 1991 (Box 37)
  - Beer and Wine Tax 1992 (Box 37)
  - Bell Atlantic 1994 (Box 37)
  - Bethel Baptist Church (HR 48) 1993 (Box 37)
  - Bills-Misc. 1994 (Box 37)
  - Bill Singletary Jr. (HJR 64) 1990 (Box 37)
  - Binding Arbitration 1993 (Box 37)
  - Bingo (HB 574) 1992 (Box 37)
  - Birth-Related Neurological Injury 1995 (Box 37)
  - Blood Alcohol Content 1994 (Box 37)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield 1994 (Box 37)
  - Board of Education 1988-1989 (Box 37)
  - Bon Air Juvenile Budget 1995-1996 (Box 37)
  - Bon Air Learning Center 1995-1996 (Box 37)
  - Bonding-Powhite (HB 852) 1986 (Box 37)
  - Bonds-Debt 1997 (Box 37)
  - Bonds-South Carolina vs. Baker (HJR 53) 1990 (Box 37)
  - Bonds/Stadium Arena (HB 2741 and 2552) 1997 (Box 38)
  - BPOL 1995-1996 (Box 38)
  - BPW 1995 (Box 38)
  - Breast Cancer (HB 240) 1994 (Box 38)
  - Bruce Jamerson 1995 (Box 38)
  - Budget Amendments 1991-1996 (Box 38)
  - Budget Amendment-Bon Air 1996, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - Budget Amendment-Chesterfield Detention Home 1996 (Box 38)
  - Budget Amendment Court Case 1996 (Box 38)
  - Budget Amendment-John Tyler 1 and 2 1996 (Box 38)
  - Budget Amendment-Powhatan National Guard Armory 1996 (Box 38)
  - Budget Amendment-School Nursing Services 1996 (Box 38)
  - Budget Amendment-Recordation Tax 1993 (Box 38)
  - Budget Amendment-Seed lab 1996 (Box 38)
  - Budget 1992-1995 (Box 38)
  - Budget Letters 1995 (Box 38)
  - Budget/Education Fund 1989 (Box 38)
  - Budget/State Bonus Offer DMV State Inspection 1996 (Box 38)
  - Building Code Alarm System (HB 413) 1986 (Box 38)
  - Building Code Discovery (HB 1137) 1992 (Box 38)
  - Cameras in the Courtroom 1992 (Box 38)
  - Campaign Finance Disclosure 1996 (Box 38)
  - Campaign Finance/Governors Proposal 1993 (Box 38)
  - Caret 1991-1992 (Box 38)
  - Carpal Tunnel Merge Letter 1997 (Box 38)
  - Cash Proffer Case 1994 (Box 38)
  - Casinos/Riverboat 1995 (Box 38)
  - Caucus 1993 (Box 38)
  - CDL/Variances (HB 641) 1992 (Box 38)
  - Cedarwoods-Powhatan (HB 11) 1996 (Box 38)
  - Central Virginia Caucus 1995 (Box 38)
  - Central Virginia Caucus 1997 (Box 39)
  - Central Virginia ETU (HB 1407) 1985 (Box 39)
  - Central Virginia Waste Management Resolution (HJR 244) 1992 (Box 39)
  - Charter for Chesterfield (HB 1254) 1991 (Box 39)
  - Charter Schools 1997 (Box 39)
  - Charts-John's Bills Chesterfield Package 1996-1997 (Box 39)
  - Chesapeake Bay Act 1988-1990 (Box 39)
  - Chesapeake Bay 1991-1992 (Box 39)
  - Chesterfield Agenda Budget Material 1994-1996 (Box 39)
  - Chesterfield Alternative 1991 (Box 39)
  - Chesterfield Charter (HB 1158) 1989 (Box 39)
  - Chesterfield Charter (HB 1159) 1989 (Box 39)
  - Chesterfield County 1992-1994 (Box 39)
  - Chesterfield County Courts 1995 (Box 39)
  - Chesterfield County Legislative Program 1995 (Box 39)
  - Chesterfield County Soils 1984-1993 (Box 39)
  - Chesterfield Package 1996 (Box 39)
  - Chesterfield Program 1994-1995 (Box 40)
  - Chesterfield School Bond Issue 1988 (Box 40)
  - Chesterfield Schools 1991 (Box 40)
  - Chesterfield/State Budget 1995 (Box 40)
  - Child Abuse 1994 (Box 40)
  - CHRON File 1988 (Box 40)
  - Cigarette Tax Reporting (HB 610) 1996 (Box 40)
  - Cigarette Tax (HB 495) 1994 (Box 40)
  - CIM (HB 1007) 1996 (Box 40)
  - Cindy Smith 1995 (Box 40)
  - Circuit Court Judge 1997 (Box 40)
  - CIT/CIM (HJR 109) 1994 (Box 40)
  - Clean Air 1994 (Box 40)
  - Clover Hill (HJR 808) 1993 (Box 40)
  - Coal and Energy 1993 (Box 40)
  - Coal and Energy Commission 1994 (Box 40)
  - College Recommendations 1992 (Box 40)
  - College and University Correspondence 1995 (Box 40)
  - Columbia HCA 1997 (Box 40)
  - Commissioners of Revenue Correspondence 1995 (Box 40)
  - Commissioner of Agriculture 1996 (Box 40)
  - Communication Services (HB 607) 1996 (Box 40)
  - Community Bonds (HB 2284) 1993 (Box 40)
  - Community Development Authorities (HB 2284) 1993 (Box 40)
  - Community Development District 1993 (Box 40)
  - Comprehensive Prevention Plan (HB 637) 1990 (Box 40)
  - Comprehensive Plan Density (HB 1665) 1991 (Box 40)
  - Computer/Machinery and Tools (HB 638) 1990-1991 (Box 41)
  - Concerned Women for America 1992 (Box 41)
  - Condemnation Commissioners (HB 640) 1992 (Box 41)
  - Conference Committee Meeting (SB 2003) 1991 (Box 41)
  - Congrats 1993 (Box 41)
  - Congressional District Plan 1991 (Box 41)
  - Constituent Concerns 1994 (Box 41)
  - Constituents Letters 1993 (Box 41)
  - Constituent Services 1994 (Box 41)
  - Constitutional Amendment Section 2 Article 4 1994 (Box 41)
  - Constitutional Amendment Statue of Repose, Limitations 1993 (Box 41)
  - Construction Management Chesterfield County Schools 1989 (Box 41)
  - Consumer Real Estate Settlement Protection Act 1996-1997 (Box 41)
  - Contract Auditing (HB 401) 1996 (Box 41)
  - Contract Collections (HB 402) 1996 (Box 41)
  - Contractors Board (HB 1930) 1993 (Box 41)
  - Contractors (HB 632) 1990 (Box 41)
  - Contractors Licenses (HB 799) 1994 (Box 41)
  - Coop Ext. Services 1992 (Box 41)
  - Co Patron Bills 1988 (Box 41)
  - Co Patron Bills 1994 (Box 41)
  - C.I.B. 1992-1996 (Box 41)
  - C.I.B. Subcommittee-Pornography 1995-1996 (Box 41)
  - Corporate Income Tax (HB 798) 1994 (Box 41)
  - Corrections-Budget Amendment-Telephone Service for Inmates 1997 (Box 41)
  - Corrections-%of Blacks Incarcerated 1997 (Box 41)
  - Correspondence 1989 (Box 41)
  - Correspondence 1989 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Any Willing Provider 1995 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Arts 1995 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-BPOL 1995 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Budget Amendments 1996 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Charter Schools 1995 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Chesterfield Town Meeting 1996 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Confederate Grave Sites 1996 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-CSB's 1995 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Dental Hygienist 1996 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Educational Libraries 1995 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Educational Mandates (HB 797) 1995 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-From Elected Officials or State Officials 1997 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-English as Official Language 1996 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Extension Service 1995 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Goals 2,000 1996 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Guidance Counselors 1995 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Human Rights Bill 1995 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-IOLTA 1995 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-MCV Hospital 1996 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Misc. Bills 1995 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-OB/GYN's 1996 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Parental Notification 1996 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence-Recommendation 1996 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence-Riverboat Gambling 1995 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence-SB 137 1996 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence-SB 898-Truckers 1995 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence-State Income Pay Plan 1995 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence-Student Requests 1996 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence-Tax Cuts 1995 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence-Teacher Awards 1996 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence-VTAG 1995 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence-Workforce Transaction Act 1995 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence-Wythe Prison 1995 (Box 43)
  - County Program 1993 (Box 43)
  - County of Shenandoah Civic Center (HB 2165-2166) 1993 (Box 43)
  - County Restoration 1990 (Box 43)
  - Court Order/Weapons (HB 96) 1991 (Box 43)
  - Credit Cards Revisions 1997 (Box 43)
  - Crisis Pregnancy Center (HB 636) 1990 (Box 43)
  - Daily Rental (HB 636) 1990 (Box 43)
  - Day Care 1992 (Box 43)
  - December-Correspondence 1987-1996 (Box 43)
  - Defensive Medicine (SJ 159) 1994 (Box 44)
  - Definition of Cities and Towns (HB 218) 1992 (Box 44)
  - Definitions Used in Land Use Statues 1991 (Box 44)
  - Delinquent Property Ads (HB 512) 1982 (Box 44)
  - Dental Hygienists (HB 973) 1984, 1992 (Box 44)
  - Dept. of Agriculture/Budget 1987 (Box 44)
  - Dept. of Taxation Forms (HB 405) 1996 (Box 44)
  - Design Bill (HB 1661) 1995 (Box 44)
  - Diet and Nutrition 1994 (Box 44)
  - Dietitians/Nutritionists (HB 2191) 1995 (Box 44)
  - Dillon Rule 1992 (Box 44)
  - Directory-Va. Newspapers 1993 (Box 44)
  - Disability Bills 1993 (Box 44)
  - Disabilities 1994 (Box 44)
  - Disabled Parking Space (HB 2870) 1997 (Box 44)
  - Disposition of Tax Return (HB 1056) 1988 (Box 44)
  - Disney 1994 (Box 44)
  - Disney-Correspondence 1994 (Box 44)
  - Disney Opposition 1994 (Box 44)
  - Distribution of ABC Profits (HB 737) 1992 (Box 44)
  - Dr. Daniel Crooks, Jr. 1992 (Box 45)
  - Dr. Richardson (HJR 239) 1987 (Box 45)
  - Drainage Bill (HB 807) 1983 (Box 45)
  - DRI/VA Power 1991-1995 (Box 45)
  - Drinking Age (HB 300) 1993 (Box 45)
  - Drivers License (HB 405) 1990 (Box 45)
  - Drugs-Crime 1992 (Box 45)
  - Drug Switching 1997 (Box 45)
  - Drunk Driving-Blood Test (HB 916) 1984 (Box 45)
  - DUI 1992-1993 (Box 45)
  - Early Intervention (HB 2715) 1997 (Box 45)
  - Early Intervention Merge 1997 (Box 45)
  - Educational Mandates (HB 797) 1994 (Box 45)
  - Earned Income Tax Credits 1997 (Box 45)
  - Education 1994-1997 (Box 45)
  - Education Funding 1992 (Box 45)
  - Elderly 1993 (Box 45)
  - Elected School Boards 1992-1994 (Box 45)
  - Elections/Abstracts (HB 404) 1996 (Box 45)
  - Eminent Domain Commissioners (HB 819) (Box 45)
  - Employment Tax Credit 1992 (Box 45)
  - Endangered Species Act/Budget 1987 (Box 45)
  - Endangered Species 1990 (Box 45)
  - Enterprise Zones 1994 (Box 45)
  - Ephedrine 1997 (Box 45)
  - Eppington 1990 (Box 45)
  - Ethics (HB 929) 1982 (Box 45)
  - Exempt from Property Taxation Railway Historical Society 1986 (Box 45)
  - Extension Letters 1992 (Box 45)
  - Extension Service 1992-1993 (Box 45)
  - Extra Bills-Copies 1994 (Box 45)
  - Family Building Act 1992-1993 (Box 45)
  - Family Court 1994 (Box 45)
  - Family Foundation 1993 (Box 45)
  - Family Foundation-VSHL 1993 (Box 45)
  - Fax Copies 1992 (Box 45)
  - Fax Covers 1994 (Box 45)
  - February Correspondence 1992-1994 (Box 45)
  - February Correspondence 1987, 1995-1996 (Box 46)
  - Film Industry 1993 (Box 46)
  - Finance-Sub, Deboer 1996 (Box 46)
  - Firearm Discharge 1996 (Box 46)
  - Focus Forward Survey 1996 (Box 46)
  - FOI/VRS 1992 (Box 46)
  - For Votes 1988 (Box 46)
  - Forest Stewardship (HJR 121) 1996 (Box 46)
  - Fort Pickett Merge Letter 1997 (Box 46)
  - Freedom of Information 1995 (Box 46)
  - General Correspondence 1995-1996 (Box 46)
  - General Correspondence-Answered 1996-1997 (Box 46)
  - General Correspondence-Unanswered 1997 (Box 46)
  - General Obligation Bonds 1992 (Box 46)
  - Girls Clover Hill Tennis Team 1995 (Box 46)
  - GIS 1995 (Box 46)
  - Goals 2,000 1997 (Box 46)
  - Goats Milk 1992-1994 (Box 46)
  - Governor's J.J. Package 1996 (Box 46)
  - Governor's Language Academics 1995 (Box 46)
  - Governor's School 1993 (Box 46)
  - Governor Allen Speech 1995 (Box 47)
  - Governor Wilder 1993 (Box 47)
  - Government Lobbyists 1994 (Box 47)
  - Grayson Commission 1989 (Box 47)
  - Grayson Commission-Hearing Packet 1989-1990 (Box 47)
  - Greater Richmond Taxfare Study 1996 (Box 47)
  - Gun Bills 1992 (Box 47)
  - Gun Control 1993 (Box 47)
  - Gun Control-Correspondence 1993 (Box 47)
  - Gun-Control Correspondence 1995 (Box 47)
  - Gun Control-Information 1993 (Box 47)
  - Guns-One Gun A Month 1993 (Box 47)
  - Gypsy Moth 1982 (Box 47)
  - Handbills 1996 (Box 47)
  - Handicapped Parking (HB 290) 1992 (Box 47)
  - Harper Case 1995 (Box 47)
  - HBAV 1996 (Box 47)
  - HB 438 1986 (Box 47)
  - HB 1163 1987 (Box 47)
  - Health Care 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Health Care Providers 1992 (Box 48)
  - Health Insurance Credits 1992 (Box 48)
  - Health Related Correspondence 1997 (Box 48)
  - Heather Studios 1987 (Box 48)
  - Hemophilia 1997 (Box 48)
  - Henricus Commending (HJR 32) 1992 (Box 48)
  - Higher Education Budget Amendment 1996-1997 (Box 48)
  - Higher Education 1993 (Box 48)
  - Higher Education 1997 (Box 48)
  - High Voltage Lines (HB 818) 1996 (Box 48)
  - Historic Richmond 1990 (Box 48)
  - HMO's (HB 2785-2789) 1997 (Box 48)
  - Home Educators Association of Va. 1992-1993 (Box 48)
  - Homeless 1992 (Box 48)
  - Homosexuality 1992 (Box 48)
  - Hospital Acquisition Oversight 1997 (Box 48)
  - Hospital Productivity Profile 1994 (Box 48)
  - House Clerk 1994 (Box 48)
  - House of Delegates/Page Application 1987 (Box 48)
  - House Resolutions 1992 (Box 48)
  - Housing Credit Deferral (HB 1474) 1996 (Box 48)
  - Impact Fees (HB 1245) 1991 (Box 48)
  - Impact Fees/Roads (HB 209) 1992 (Box 48)
  - Impact Tax 1991 (Box 48)
  - Incest 1993 (Box 48)
  - Income Tax/Credit (HB 672) 1990 (Box 48)
  - Income Tax (HB 671) 1990 (Box 48)
  - Income Tax (HB 771) 1992 (Box 48)
  - Insurance 1992 (Box 48)
  - Insurance Subrogation 1994 (Box 48)
  - Insurers Absolved from Liability (HB 817) 1996 (Box 48)
  - Interbasin Transfer Act 1981-1985 (Box 48)
  - Interbasin Transfer Act 1982 (Box 48)
  - Interstate Succession 1982 (Box 49)
  - Initiatives and Referendums 1993 (Box 49)
  - Investment in State Treasury (HB 1406) 1985 (Box 49)
  - Investment Tax Credits (HB 798) 1992-1993 (Box 49)
  - Investor Tax (HB 810) 1996-1997 (Box 49)
  - Invitro Fertilization (HB 990) 1992 (Box 49)
  - IOLTA 1994 (Box 49)
  - Issuance of Refunding Bond (HB 1240) 1985 (Box 49)
  - January-Correspondence 1987-1989, 1993-1993 (Box 49)
  - John Boyer-Dr. Nelson Chesterfield County Health Department 1995 (Box 49)
  - John's Notes: VGIN 1997 (Box 49)
  - Johnston-Willis Hospital 1994 (Box 49)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying the Taxation of Dental Equip. 1998 (Box 49)
  - Judge to be Appointed 1996 (Box 50)
  - Judicial Barbarism 1993 (Box 50)
  - Judges 1993 (Box 50)
  - Judges and Davenport-Gov's Commission on Juvenile Reform 1995-1996 (Box 50)
  - Judges J and D 1997 (Box 50)
  - July-Correspondence 1987-1988, 1992-1996 (Box 50)
  - June-Correspondence 1987-1988 (Box 50)
  - June-Correspondence 1993-1996 (Box 51)
  - Juvenile (HB 1473) 1996 (Box 51)
  - Kappa Sigma UVA 1995 (Box 51)
  - Juvenile Justice Va. Commission on Youth 1996 (Box 51)
  - Knowles/Falkirk 1995 (Box 51)
  - Labor Bills 1993 (Box 51)
  - Lag Pay-Budget Amendment 1997 (Box 51)
  - Lag Pay Merge Letter 1997 (Box 51)
  - Lake Gaston 1993 (Box 51)
  - Land Distributing Activities 1994 (Box 51)
  - Landfills 1987 (Box 51)
  - Land Use (HB 1078) 1990 (Box 51)
  - Legislation (old bills) 1993 (Box 51)
  - Legislation 1993 (Box 51)
  - Legislative Packet 1992 (Box 51)
  - Legislative Program for Chesterfield County 1994 (Box 51)
  - Legislative Summary 1994 (Box 51)
  - Leland B. Anderson (HJR 29) 1992 (Box 51)
  - Liability Insurance (HB 160) 1997 (Box 51)
  - Libraries 1994 (Box 52)
  - License Revocation Bill 1993 (Box 52)
  - Limited Reduction of Verdict (HB 1520) 1989 (Box 52)
  - Litter Tax (HB 1147) 1987 (Box 52)
  - Lobby/Government (HB 1586) 1993 (Box 52)
  - Lobbyists 1992 (Box 52)
  - Local Assessments (HB 403) 1996 (Box 52)
  - Local Government-Counties, Cities, and Towns 1986-1987 (Box 52)
  - Local Government-Position Statements 1988 (Box 52)
  - Local Grievance Procedure (HB 437) 1986 (Box 52)
  - Lottery-Private 1994 (Box 52)
  - Lottery-Profits 1993 (Box 52)
  - Lottery-Sales Tax 1995 (Box 52)
  - Lottery-Speech 1987 (Box 52)
  - Lutheran Church Positions 1992 (Box 52)
  - Lythrum Salicaria 1993 (Box 52)
  - Luzik Complaints 1996 (Box 52)
  - Magnolia Grange 1990 (Box 52)
  - Malicious Wounding Assault and Battery 1995 (Box 52)
  - M.A.M.A 1992 (Box 52)
  - Managed Care 1995 (Box 52)
  - March-Correspondence 1987-1988, 1992-1996 (Box 52)
  - Marine Patrol (HB 912) 1982 (Box 53)
  - Masonic Temple (HB 70) 1994 (Box 53)
  - May-Correspondence 1987-1988, 1992-1996 (Box 53)
  - MCV-Hospitals Authority 1997 (Box 53)
  - Meat and Poultry Inspection 1992 (Box 53)
  - Mechanics Liens (HB 972) 1992 (Box 53)
  - Medicaid 1996 (Box 53)
  - Medicaid-Tax Supplements 1992 (Box 53)
  - Medical Malpractice (HB 1986) 1989 (Box 53)
  - Medical Malpractice 1993 (Box 53)
  - Medical Malpractice (SB 508) 1994 (Box 53)
  - Medical Malpractice 1997 (Box 53)
  - Medical Society 1997 (Box 53)
  - Medical Waste Incinerators 1992 (Box 53)
  - Menus 1992-1994 (Box 53)
  - Merchants Capital (HB 1376) 1987 (Box 53)
  - Merchants Capital Tax (HB 687) 1988 (Box 53)
  - Merge Letter (HB 160) 1997 (Box 53)
  - Merge Letter (HB 2234) 1997 (Box 53)
  - Merge Letter (HB 2455) 1997 (Box 53)
  - Midlothian High School Tennis (HR 40) 1990 (Box 53)
  - Midwives 1993 (Box 54)
  - Midwives-Third Party 1993 (Box 54)
  - Misc. Bills 1994-1995 (Box 54)
  - Misc. Utility 1994 (Box 54)
  - Missouri vs. Jenkins 1995 (Box 54)
  - Mobile Homes (HB 511) 1982 (Box 54)
  - Montessori School-Day Care Regulations 1992 (Box 54)
  - Morris Industries 1992 (Box 54)
  - Mother's For Daycare 1992 (Box 54)
  - Motor Vehicle Carriers 1993 (Box 54)
  - Motor Vehicle Warranty (HB 816) 1996 (Box 54)
  - Museum of the Confederacy 1995 (Box 54)
  - Nasdaq 1994 (Box 55)
  - Navigable Streams 1992 (Box 55)
  - Neighborhood Assistance 1996 (Box 55)
  - Neshap-Asbestos (HB 527) 1992 (Box 55)
  - Newsclippings 1987 (Box 55)
  - Newspaper Articles 1996 (Box 55)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1990-1995 (Box 55)
  - Newspapers 1992-1994 (Box 55)
  - News Releases 1991 (Box 55)
  - Non-Prescription Drugs (HB 1477) 1996 (Box 55)
  - Notary Public 1994 (Box 55)
  - Notary Public Study (HJR 467) 1995 (Box 55)
  - Not For Profit Medical 1995 (Box 55)
  - November Correspondence 1987-1988, 1992-1993 (Box 55)
  - November-Correspondence 1994-1996 (Box 56)
  - No Wake Zones (HB 820) 1996 (Box 56)
  - Nurses 1992 (Box 56)
  - Nutrient Policy 1997 (Box 56)
  - OBGYN Services (HB 1472) 1996 (Box 56)
  - October-Correspondence 1987-1988, 1992 (Box 56)
  - October Correspondence 1992-1996 (Box 57)
  - Old Age Tax Redemption (HB 1469) 1996 (Box 57)
  - Optometrists 1992 (Box 57)
  - Optometrists 1995 (Box 57)
  - Outdoor Advertising 1997 (Box 57)
  - Page Applications 1987 (Box 57)
  - Parental Consent 1993 (Box 57)
  - Parental Notification (HB 958) 1992 (Box 57)
  - Parental Responsibility Act 1995 (Box 57)
  - Parental Rights 1997 (Box 57)
  - Pari-Mutual Betting 1992 (Box 57)
  - Patient Protection Act 1996 (Box 57)
  - Patron Report 1982-1993 (Box 57)
  - Performance Based Rates (HB 497) 1996 (Box 57)
  - Personal Property Tax-Zoo Animals (HB 494) 1994 (Box 57)
  - Personnel Act (HB 283) 1994 (Box 57)
  - Pesticides (SB 1070) 1995 (Box 57)
  - Pesticide Control Board (HB 645) 1992 (Box 57)
  - Pesticide Waste Disposal 1990 (Box 57)
  - Peter Swisher 1992 (Box 57)
  - Pharmacy-Ancillary Problem 1995 (Box 57)
  - Pharmacy-Freedom of Choice (HB 1977) 1995 (Box 57)
  - Pharmacy 1995 (Box 57)
  - Photos 1993 (Box 57)
  - Planned Parenthood-Family Matters 1994 (Box 57)
  - Pledge Bonds 1992 (Box 57)
  - Pocahontas Park (HB 376) 1996 (Box 57)
  - Population Growth and Development 1967-1977 (Box 57)
  - Population Growth and Development 1984 (Box 57)
  - Population Growth and Development 1988-1994 (Box 58)
  - Population Growth and Development 1993 (Box 59)
  - Portable Signs (HB 1495) 1993 (Box 59)
  - Postage 1997 (Box 59)
  - Postage Accounts 1995 (Box 59)
  - Poverty 1994 (Box 59)
  - Power Lines 1994 (Box 59)
  - Powers of Lt. Government (HJR 22) 1992-1993 (Box 59)
  - Powhatan County 1992 (Box 59)
  - Powhite 1997 (Box 59)
  - Powhite Tolls (HJR 51) 1996 (Box 59)
  - Prayer 1991 (Box 59)
  - Press Releases 1993 (Box 59)
  - Prevention Plan (HB 637) 1990 (Box 59)
  - Privatization of Government Services 1995 (Box 59)
  - Privileges and Elections 1988, 1992-1997 (Box 59)
  - Privileges and Elections-Campaign Finance 1996-1997 (Box 59)
  - Procurement Bids (HB 493) 1994 (Box 59)
  - Product Liability 1995 (Box 59)
  - Projects-General Obligation Financing 1992 (Box 59)
  - Prompt Payment 1985 (Box 59)
  - Property/Pocahontas (SB 737) 1995 (Box 59)
  - Proration/Personal Property Refunds (HB 1376) 1991 (Box 59)
  - Public Broadcasting 1992 (Box 59)
  - Public Education 1991 (Box 59)
  - Public Hearings 1985 (Box 59)
  - Public Hearing-Solid Waste Authority (HB 572) 1992 (Box 59)
  - Public Procurement (HB 1714) 1995 (Box 59)
  - Public Service Company (HB 280) 1994 (Box 59)
  - Pump of Virginia-Bob Young 1995-1996 (Box 59)
  - Radar Detectors (HB 219) 1992-1996 (Box 59)
  - Ratite 1997 (Box 59)
  - Real Estate Appraisers 1992 (Box 59)
  - Real Estate Closings 1977 (Box 59)
  - Real Estate Disclosure (HB 1493) 1993 (Box 59)
  - Real Estate Disclosure-Powhatan (HB 225) 1994 (Box 59)
  - Real Property Disclosures (HB 1411) 1989 (Box 59)
  - Recommendations 1994 (Box 59)
  - Recycling 1992 (Box 59)
  - Rebecca Wyngaard 1992 (Box 59)
  - Recover Fees (HB 1929) 1993 (Box 59)
  - Redistricting 1991-1996 (Box 60)
  - Redistricting/Census 2000 1994-1997 (Box 60)
  - Religious Freedom Restoration Act 1997 (Box 60)
  - Rental of Film and Videotapes (HB 1163) 1987 (Box 60)
  - Repealers 1986 (Box 60)
  - Reports 1992-1993 (Box 60)
  - Requests 1994 (Box 60)
  - Residential Disclosure Act (HB 802) 1994 (Box 60)
  - Resumes from Swisher 1992 (Box 60)
  - Retirement Deduction Income Tax (HB 279) 1994 (Box 60)
  - Retirement System 1993 (Box 60)
  - Retirees (HB 1564) 1995 (Box 60)
  - Revenue Bonds (HB 492) 1983 (Box 60)
  - Revenue Data 1997 (Box 60)
  - Reward Reimbursement (HB 1541) 1987 (Box 60)
  - Reward Reimbursement (HB 659) 1988 (Box 60)
  - Richmond Center Budget Amendment 1996 (Box 60)
  - Richmond Charter 1997 (Box 60)
  - Richmond City 1992 (Box 60)
  - Richmond International Airport 1995 (Box 60)
  - Right to Farm 1995 (Box 60)
  - Right to Work 1993 (Box 60)
  - Riverboat Gaming 1993-1996 (Box 60)
  - RMA 1992 (Box 60)
  - Road Access (HB 1373) 1987 (Box 60)
  - Route 288 1992 (Box 60)
  - Route 895 1996 (Box 60)
  - Ryland J. Hughes 1993 (Box 60)
  - Sales Tax 1992 (Box 61)
  - Sales Tax/ABC (HB 285) 1994 (Box 61)
  - Sales Tax Lottery 1994 (Box 61)
  - Sales and Use Tax 1986 (Box 61)
  - Sanders vs. Scott 1992 (Box 61)
  - SB 1027 (Box 61)
  - SB 2003 (Box 61)
  - SCC Resolution 1993 (Box 61)
  - Schools/Birth Certificate (HB 1666) 1991 (Box 61)
  - School Board Districts (HB 661) 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - School Board Salaries (HB 1588) 1993 (Box 61)
  - School Bus Drivers (HB 262) 1986 (Box 61)
  - Schools-Facilities 1990 (Box 61)
  - School Impact Fees 1992 (Box 61)
  - Seed Law (HB 1139) 1994 (Box 61)
  - Seed Tree (HB 612) 1996 (Box 61)